A lot has been said by people concerning how the church,
'Synagogue' came into being.
Some people questioned my foundation, my mentor,
my educational background and my calling as a man of God.
I am not showing this documentary because people questioned
my foundation, my background, my mentor,
my educational background, my calling as a man of God.
I am showing it because it is God's time. That is, it is an act of God.
Stay blessed and watch.
This is my story
Prophet T.B. Joshua
This is Prophet T.B. Joshua at the prayer mountain.
Guided by the Holy Spirit, Prophet T.B. Joshua came to this prayer mountain to seek the face of God.
Like prophets of old, he fasted and prayed for 40 days and 40 nights,
as prayer and fasting opens the door for God to enter.
It was at this very prayer mountain that Prophet T.B. Joshua
received divine anointing from God to start his ministry.
As he raises his hand to Heaven and then falls prostrating to pray,
he received a covenant from God concerning his calling.
Only he and God know the divine message that was revealed to him at that moment.
Concerning this experience, Prophet T.B. Joshua said, ""I was in a trance for three consecutive days.
Then, I saw a hand that pointed a Bible to my heart and the Bible entered my heart.
And my former heart immersed with the Bible immediately.
Then, the awareness came and I saw the apostles and prophets of old
with someone who I could not see his head
because he was tall to the Heaven and suspended
which I believe was our Lord Jesus Christ sitting in their midst.
I also saw myself in their midst.
After a while, I saw a hand of the same tall man. I could not behold his face
which was glittering with an unimaginable light.
But other apostles I could see their faces, particularly Apostles Peter and Paul,
Prophets Moses and Elijah, and others.
Their names were boldly written on their chest.
I heard a voice saying, "I am your God.
I am giving you a divine commission to go and carry out the work of the Heavenly Father".
At the same time, the same hand of the tall man gave me a small cross
and a big Bible - bigger than the one that entered my heart -
with a promise that as I keep pressing in His time and name, I will be given a bigger cross.
But if I fail, the opposite would occur.
I also heard a voice of the same tall man - I could not see his head -
saying, "I am the Lord your God, who was and who is, Jesus Christ,
giving orders to all the apostles and prophets".
The same voice said to me, "I would show you the wonderful ways, I would reveal myself through you
in teaching, preaching, miracles, signs and wonders for the salvation of souls".
Since then, I have been receiving in my vision every year according to my faithfulness to God, a bigger cross.
That means to me more responsibilities.
The Bible that entered my heart symbolizes Spirit and life, the Holy Spirit.
God's Word is Spirit and life. He does nothing without His Word.
The Book of Romans 8:16 says:
"God's Spirit joins Himself to our spirit to declare that we are children of God".
This divine anointing is performed by God Himself on all
who have the wonderful privilege of becoming His children.
It accompanies the conversion of those who trust in Christ.
Paul said that the Spirit indwells every believer and His presence is the guarantee of our future glory in Heaven
according to the Book of 2 Corinthians 1:21-22.
As a result of this indwelling presence, we have the ability to become more like Christ
in accordance with 2 Corinthians 3:17-18.
We who are born of God have no excuse of remaining as we are.
We can be increasingly conformed to the image of Christ
by yielding ourselves to God's anointing, the Holy Spirit, who dwells in our hearts.
Father, thank You for Your Spirit.
Fill us with His love and power.
Change us into Christ's own image day by day and hour by hour.
Remember, the Father gave us the Spirit to make us like His Son.
These are the pictures you will bring out and show people.
By the time the glory of God is revealed to the world and other countries start coming,
at that time, I will not have the time to come here again.
I will have my own prayer mountain"".
The man of God said that by the time the glory of God is revealed in his ministry
and people from other countries start coming,
he will no longer have the time to visit this prayer mountain.
And that in the future, he will have his own prayer mountain.
This is a picture of Prophet T.B. Joshua praying for people
after just having returned from a 40 day and 40 night fast at the prayer mountain.